Parodies, [ca. 1850-1950] PN6110 .P3
Lilly Library
- Parodies, [ca. 1850-1950]
  - Shakespeare, William, 1564-1616., 11 envelopes (Box 6, Item 48)
    - "Blow, blow, thou winter wind," from As You Like It (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 2)
    - "But wherefore do not you a mightier way" from Sonnet 16 (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 2)
    - "By the simplicity of Venus' doves-" from A Midsummer Night's Dream (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 2)
    - "Come, shall we go and kill us venison?" from As You Like It (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 2)
    - "Come unto these yellow sands," from the Tempest (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 2)
    - Crabbèd Age and Youth. "Crabbèd Age and Youth" from The Passionate Pilgrim (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 2)
    - "Farewell! a long farewell, to all my greatness!" from King Henry VIII (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 2)
    - "Fear no more the heat o' the sun," from Cymbeline (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 2)
    - "A fool, a fool!-I met a fool i' the forest," from As You Like It (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 2)
    - "For shame, be friends, and join for that you jar." From Titus Andronicus (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 2)
    - "Friends, Romans, countrymen, lend me your ears:" from Julius Caesar (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 2)
    - "Friends, Romans, countrymen, lend me your ears:" from Julius Caesar (cont.) (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 3)
    - "From the east to western Ind," from As you Like It; also "If a hart do lack a hind" (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 3)
    - Full Fathom Five Thy Father Lies. "Full fathom five they father lies;" from the Tempest (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 3)
    - "Good name in man and woman, dear my lord," from Othello (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 3)
    - "Hark! hark! the lark at heaven's gate sings," from Cymbeline (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 3)
    - "Her lily hand her rosy cheek lies under," from Lucrece (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 3)
    - "How can my Muse want subject to invent," from Sonnet 38 (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 3)
    - "I am that merry wanderer of the night." from A Midsummer Night's Dream (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 3)
    - "I do remember an apothecary," from Romeo and Juliet (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 3)
    - "I know a bank where the wild thyme blows," from A Midsummer Night's Dream (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 3)
    - "I saw him beat the surges under him," from the Tempest (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 3)
    - "I will tell you. The barge she sat in, like a burnish'd throne," from Antony and Cleopatra (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 3)
    - "If it were done, when 'tis done, then't were well" from Macbeth (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 3)
    - "If there be nothing new, but that which is" from Sonnet 59 (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 3)
    - "If we offend, it is with our good will." from A Midsummer Night's Dream (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 4)
    - "Is this a dagger, which I see before me," from Macbeth (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 4)
    - "It is the cause, it is the cause, my soul,--" from Othello (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 4)
    - "It was a lover and his lass," from As You Like It (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 4)
    - "I'the commonwealth I would by contraries" from the Tempest (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 4)
    - "Lo! in the orient when the gracious light" from Sonnet 7 (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 4)
    - "Look here, upon this picture, and on this;" from Hamlet (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 4)
    - "Look, when a painter would surpass the life," from Venus and Adonis (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 4)
    - "The moon shines bright.-In such a night as this," from the Merchant of Venice (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 4)
    - "Most potent, grave, and reverend signiors," from Othello (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 4)
    - "My father had a daughter lov'd a man," from Twelfth Night (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 4)
    - "My gentle Puck, come hither: thou remember'st" from A Midsummer Night's Dream (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 4)
    - "Now entertain conjecture of a time," from King Henry V (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 4)
    - "Now is the winter of our discontent" from King Richard III (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 4)
    - "O!-And I, forsooth, in love! I, that have been loves' whip;" from Love's Labour's Lost (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 4)
    - "O now, for ever, Farewell the tranquil mind! farewell content! from Othello (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 5)
    - "O! that this too too solid flesh would melt," from Hamlet (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 5)
    - "Our revels now are ended. These our actors," from the Tempest (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 5)
    - "The quality of mercy is not strained," from the Merchant of Venice (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 5)
    - "Romans, countrymen, and lovers! Hear me..." from Julius Caesar (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 5)
    - Shakespeare's Epitaph. "Good friend, for Jesus sake forbeare" (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 5)
    - "Shall I compare thee to a summer's day?" from Sonnet 43 (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 5)
    - "Sigh no more ladies, sigh no more," from Much Ado About Nothing (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 5)
    - "Signior Antonio, many a time and oft," from the Merchant of Venice (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 5)
    - "So oft have I invok'd thee for my Muse," from Sonnet 78 (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 5)
    - "Soft you, a word or two, before you go." from Othello (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 5)
    - "Speak the speech, I pray you, as I pronounced..." from Hamlet (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 5)
    - "Take, O! take those lips away," from Measure for Measure (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 6)
    - "Tell me, where is fancy bred," from the Merchant of Venice (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 6)
    - "That very time I saw (but thou couldst not)," from A Midsummer Night's Dream (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 6)
    - "There,--my blessing with you;" from Hamlet (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 6)
    - "There were two honours lost, yours, and your son's:" from Henry IV (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 6)
    - "Therefore, fair Hermia, question your desires;" from A Midsummer Night's Dream (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 6)
    - "This royal throne of kings, this scepter'd isle," from Richard II (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 6)
    - "Thou toldst me, thou didst hold him in thy hate." from Othello (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 6)
    - "'Tis now the very witching time of night," from Hamlet (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 6)
    - "To be, or not to be, that is the question:--" from Hamlet (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 6)
    - "To be, or not to be, that is the question:--" from Hamlet (cont.) (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 7)
    - "To be, or not to be, that is the question:--" from Hamlet (cont.) (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 8)
    - "To be, or not to be, that is the question:--" from Hamlet (cont.) (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 9)
    - "Tom will throw his head at them. -Avaunt, you curs!" from King Lear (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 9)
    - "Under the greenwood tree," from As You Like It (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 9)
    - "What find I here?" from The Merchant of Venice (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 9)
    - "What shall he have, that kill'd the deer?" from As You Like It (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 9)
    - "When daisies pied, and violets blue," from Love's Labours Lost (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 9)
    - "When icicles hang by the wall," from Love's Labours Lost (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 9)
    - "When shall we three." from Macbeth (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 9)
    - "When to the sessions of sweet silent thought" from Sonnet XXX (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 9)
    - "Where the bee sucks, there suck I:" from the Tempest (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 9)
    - Who is Sylvia? "Who is Sylvia? what is she" (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 9)
    - "Why is my verse so barren of new pride," from Sonnet LXXVI (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 9)
    - "You spotted snakes, with double tongue," from Midsummer Night's Dream (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 9)
    - General (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 10)
    - General (Box 6, Item 48, Envelope 11)
  - The Shan Van Vocht. "Oh! the French are on the sea,", 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 1)
  - Shelley, Percy Bysshe, 1792-1822., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 2)
    - Adonais. "I weep for Adonais--he is dead!" (Box 7, Item 2)
    - The Cloud. "I bring fresh showers for the thirsting flowers" (Box 7, Item 2)
    - The Flight of Love. "When the lamp is shatter'd" (Box 7, Item 2)
    - The Fugitives. "The waters are flashing" (Box 7, Item 2)
    - Hellas. "The world's great age begins anew" (Box 7, Item 2)
    - The Indian Serenade. "I arise from dreams of thee" (Box 7, Item 2)
    - Lines Written Among the Euganean Hills. "Many a green isle needs must be" (Box 7, Item 2)
    - My Soul is Like an Enchanted Boat. "My soul is like an enchanted boat" (Box 7, Item 2)
    - Ozymandias. "I met a traveler from an antique land" (Box 7, Item 2)
    - Revolt of Islam. (Box 7, Item 2)
    - The Sensitive Plant. "A Sensitive Plant in a garden grew" (Box 7, Item 2)
    - To a Skylark. "Hail to thee, blith spirit!" (Box 7, Item 2)
    - To Night. "Swiftly walk over the western wave" (Box 7, Item 2)
    - 'When the Lamp is Shattered.' "When the lamp is shattered" (Box 7, Item 2)
    - General. (Box 7, Item 2)
  - Shenstone, William, 1714-1763., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 3)
    - A Geological Madrigal. "I have found out a gift for my fair;" (Box 7, Item 3)
    - A Pastoral Ballad. "Ye shepherds so cheerful and gay" (Box 7, Item 3)
  - Shepherd, Nathaniel Graham, 1835-1869., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 4)
    - Roll Call. "'Corporal Green!' the Orderly cried;" (Box 7, Item 4)
  - Sheridan, R. B., 1751-1816, 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 5)
    - Glee. "This bottle's the sun of our table" (Box 7, Item 5)
    - Had I a Heart for Falsehood Framed. "Had I a heart for falsehood framed;" (Box 7, Item 5)
    - "Here's to the maiden of bashful fifteen;" (Box 7, Item 5)
    - Parody in the style of Sheridan, original poem unidentified. (Box 7, Item 5)
  - Sherman, Frank D., 1860-1916., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 6)
    - Dirge. "Let a song be softly sung;" (Box 7, Item 6)
  - Sidney, Philip, 1554-1586., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 7)
    - A Ditty. "My true-love hath my heart, and I have his" (Box 7, Item 7)
  - Sigourney, Mrs. L. H., 1791-1865., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 8)
    - Parodies in the style of Sigourney, original poems unidentified. (Box 7, Item 8)
  - Sims, George Robert, 1847-1922., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 9)
    - Ostler Joe. "I stood at eve, as the sun went down, by a grave where a woman lies" (Box 7, Item 9)
    - Parodies in the style of Ostler, original poems unidentified. (Box 7, Item 9)
  - Sims, James, 1813-1883., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 10)
    - Let us Haste to Kelvin Grove. "Let us haste to Kelvin Grove" (Box 7, Item 10)
  - Sir Patrick Spens. "The king sits in Dumferline, town,", 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 11)
  - Sitwell, Edith, 1887-1964., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 12)
    - Parody in style of Sitwell, original poem unidentified. (Box 7, Item 12)
  - Skeffington, L. S., 1771-1850., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 13)
    - Fanny of Timmol. "Sweet Fanny of Timmol! I often recur" (Box 7, Item 13)
  - Skinner, Alanson., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 14)
    - Parody in the style of Skinner, original poem unidentified. (Box 7, Item 14)
  - Smith, Alexander, 1830-1867., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 15)
    - Parody in the style of Smith, original poem unidentified. (Box 7, Item 15)
  - Smith, Belle E., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 16)
    - If I should die To-Night. "If I should die to-night" (Box 7, Item 16)
  - Smith, Edmund N., 1672-1710., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 17)
    - "So, when bright Venus yielded up her charms" (Box 7, Item 17)
  - Smith Horace, 1779-1849., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 18)
    - Address To a Mummy. "And thou hast walked about (how strange a story!)" (Box 7, Item 18)
    - George Barnwell. "George Barnwell stood at the shop-door" (Box 7, Item 18)
  - Smith, Samuel F., 1808-1895., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 19)
    - America. "My country, 'tis of thee" (Box 7, Item 19)
  - Southey, Robert, 1774-1843., 4 envelopes (Box 7, Item 20)
    - The Battle Of Blenheim. "It was a summer evening--" (Box 7, Item 20, Envelope 1)
    - The Cataract of Lodore. "How does the water" (Box 7, Item 20, Envelope 1)
    - The Cataract of Lodore. "How does the water" (Continued) (Box 7, Item 20, Envelope 2)
    - Curse of Kehama. (Box 7, Item 20, Envelope 2)
    - Father William. "'You are old, Father William,' the young man cried" (Box 7, Item 20, Envelope 2)
    - Father William. "'You are old, Father William,' the young man cried," (Cont.) (Box 7, Item 20, Envelope 3)
    - "How beautiful is night!" (Box 7, Item 20, Envelope 3)
    - The Inchcape Rock. "No stir in the air, no stir in the sea" (Box 7, Item 20, Envelope 3)
    - Inscription, "For thirty years, secluded from mankind" (Box 7, Item 20, Envelope 3)
    - The Soldier's Wife. "Weary way-wanderer, languid and sick at heart" (Box 7, Item 20, Envelope 3)
    - Vision of Judgment. (Box 7, Item 20, Envelope 3)
    - "What news, O King Offanso?" (Box 7, Item 20, Envelope 3)
    - The Widow. "Cold was the night wind; drifting fast the snows fell;" (Box 7, Item 20, Envelope 3)
    - The Widow. "Cold was the night wind; drifting fast the snows fell;" Cont. (Box 7, Item 20, Envelope 4)
    - General. (Box 7, Item 20, Envelope 4)
  - Squire, Sir John Collings, 1884-., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 21)
    - Parody in the style of Squire, original poem unidentified. (Box 7, Item 21)
  - Spencer, William Robert, 1769-1834., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 22)
    - Parody in the style of Spencer, original poem unidentified. (Box 7, Item 22)
  - Spenser, Edmund, 1552?-1599., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 23)
    - The Shepherd's Calendar. "A shepeheards boye, (no better doe him call,)" (Box 7, Item 23)
    - Parodies in the style of Spenser, original poems unidentified. (Box 7, Item 23)
  - Stedman, Edmund Clarence, 1833-1908., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 24)
    - Parody in the style of Stedman, original poem unidentified. (Box 7, Item 24)
  - Stephen, James Kenneth, 1859-1982., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 25)
    - To R.K. "Will there never come a season" (Box 7, Item 25)
  - Stevens, George Alexander, 1710-1784., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 26)
    - The Storm. "Cease, rude boreas, blust'ring railer" (Box 7, Item 26)
  - Stevenson, Robert Louis, 1850-1894., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 27)
    - Bed in Summer. "In winter I get up at night" (Box 7, Item 27)
    - Foreign Children. "Little Indian, Sioux or Crow" (Box 7, Item 27)
    - Good and Bad Children. "Children, you are very little" (Box 7, Item 27)
    - Rain. "The rain is falling all around" (Box 7, Item 27)
    - System. "Every night my prayers I say" (Box 7, Item 27)
    - A Thought. "It is very nice to think" (Box 7, Item 27)
    - To Andrew Lang. "Dear Andrew, with the brindled hair" (Box 7, Item 27)
    - Travel. "Where the golden apples grow;--" (Box 7, Item 27)
    - Whole Duty of Children. "A child should always say what's true" (Box 7, Item 27)
    - The Wind "I saw you toss the kites on high" (Box 7, Item 27)
    - Parodies in the style of Stevenson, original poems unidentified. (Box 7, Item 27)
  - Still, John., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 28)
    - Jolly Good Ale and Old. "I cannot eat but little meat -" (Box 7, Item 28)
  - Stoddard, Elizabeth Drew (Barstow), 1823-1902., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 29)
    - Parody in the style of Stoddard, original poem unidentified. (Box 7, Item 29)
  - Stoddard, Richard Henry, 1825-1903., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 30)
    - "Along the grassy slope I sit" (Box 7, Item 30)
    - Lovers' Hearts. "Full of wine, two branches of a vine" (Box 7, Item 30)
    - The Sea. "By the rolling waves I roam" (Box 7, Item 30)
    - General. (Box 7, Item 30)
  - Story, William Wetmore, 1819-1895., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 31)
    - Cleopatra. "Here, Charmian, take my bracelets:" (Box 7, Item 31)
  - Strode, William, 1600?-1645., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 32)
    - "I saw fair Chloris walk alone" (Box 7, Item 32)
    - In Commendation of Music. "When whispering strains do softly steal" (Box 7, Item 32)
  - Suckling, Sir John, 1609-1642., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 33)
    - A Ballad upon a Wedding. "I tell thee, Dick, where I have been" (Box 7, Item 33)
    - "Honest Lover whosever" (Box 7, Item 33)
    - A Session of the Poets. "A session was held the other day" (Box 7, Item 33)
    - Song. "Why so pale and wan, fond lover?" (Box 7, Item 33)
    - General. (Box 7, Item 33)
  - Summer is coming. "Summer is a-coming in!", 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 34)
  - Swift, Jonathan, 1667-1745., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 35)
    - "'Now all alone poor madam sits'" (Box 7, Item 35)
    - General. (Box 7, Item 35)
  - Swinburne, Algernon Charles, 1837-1909., 7 envelopes (Box 7, Item 36)
    - A Ballad of Burdens. "The burden of fair women. Vain delight" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 1)
    - A Ballad of Dreamland. "I hid my heart in a nest of roses" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 1)
    - Before Dawn. "Sweet life, if life were stronger" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 1)
    - "Between the sunset and the sea" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 1)
    - By the North Sea. "Sea, wind and sun, with light and sound and breath" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 1)
    - Chorus. "Before the beginning of years" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 1)
    - Clear the way! "Clear the way, my lords and lackeys! you have had your day." (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 1)
    - The Commonweal. "Men, whose fathers brave the world in arms against our isles in union" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 1)
    - Dedication. "The sea gives her shells to the shingle" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 1)
    - A Dialogue. "Death, if thou wilt, fain would I plead with thee:" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 1)
    - Dolores. "Cold eyelids that hide like a jewel" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 2)
    - Faustine. "Lean back, and get some minutes' peace:" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 2)
    - "For winter's rains and ruins are over" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 2)
    - Fragoletta. "O Love! what shall be said of thee?" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 2)
    - The Garden of Proserpine. "Here, where the world is quiet;" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 2)
    - Had I Wist. "Had I wist, when life was like a warm wind playing" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 3)
    - Hymn to Proserpine. "I have lived long enough, having seen one thing, that love hath an end;" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 3)
    - "I lift up mine eyes from the skirts of the shadow" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 3)
    - The Interpreters. "Days dawn on us that make amends for many" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 3)
    - Itylus. "Swallow, my sister, I sister swallow" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 3)
    - In a Garden. "Baby, see the flowers!" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 3)
    - Kissing Her Hair. "Kissing her hair, I sat against her feet;" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 3)
    - A Leave-taking. "Let us go hence, my songs; she will not hear." (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 3)
    - A Litany. "All the bright lights of heaven" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 3)
    - The Litany. "All the bright lights of heaven" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 3)
    - The Litany of Nations. "If with voice of words or prayers thy sons may reach thee" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 3)
    - "Lord Love went maying" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 3)
    - March, An Ode. "Ere frost-flower and snow-blossom faded and fell, and the splendor of winter had passed out of sight" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 3)
    - The Masque of Queen Bersabe. "Knights mine, all that by in hall" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 3)
    - A Match. "If love were what the rose is" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 3)
    - A Match. "If love were what the rose is" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 4)
    - The Oblation. "Ask nothing more of me, sweet;" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 4)
    - "Outside of the port ye are moored in, lying" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 4)
    - The Question. "Shall England consummate the crime" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 4)
    - A Rhyme. "Baby, if rhyme be none" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 4)
    - Rococo. "Take hands and part with laughter;" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 4)
    - The Roundel. "A roundel is wrought as a ring or a starbright sphere" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 4)
    - Satia Te Sanguine. "If you loved me ever so little" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 4)
    - A Singing Lesson. "Far-fetched and dear-bought, as the proverb rehearses" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 4)
    - The Triumph of Time. "Before our lives divide forever" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 4)
    - The Union. "Three in one, but one in three" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 4)
    - A Watch in the Night. "Watchman, what of the night? -" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 4)
    - A Word for the Navy. "Queen born of the sea, that hast borne her" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 4)
    - When the hounds of Spring. "When the hounds of spring are on winter's traces" (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 4)
    - General. (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 5)
    - General. (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 6)
    - General. (Box 7, Item 36, Envelope 7)
  - Taffy Was a Welshman. "Taffy was a Welshman, Taffy was a thief;", 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 37)
  - Tagore Sir Rabindranath, 1861-1941., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 38)
    - Parodies in the style of Tagore, original poems unidentified. (Box 7, Item 38)
  - A Tale of the Tenth Hussars. "When the sand of the lonely desert has covered the plains of strife,", 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 39)
  - Tannahill, Robert, 1774-1810., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 40)
    - Jessie, the Flower o' Dunblane. "The sun has gane down o'er the lofty Benlomond" (Box 7, Item 40)
  - Taylor, Ann., 3 envelopes (Box 7, Item 41)
  - Taylor, Bayard, 1825-1878., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 42)
    - Bedouin Love-Song. "From the desert I come to thee" (Box 7, Item 42)
  - Taylor, Jane, 1783-1824., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 43)
    - Child's Hymn of Praise. "I thank the goodness and the grace" (Box 7, Item 43)
    - The Star. "Twinkle, twinkle, little star" (Box 7, Item 43)
  - Ten Little Nigger Boys., 1 envelope (Box 7, Item 44)
  - Tennyson, Alfred Tennyson, baron, 1809-1892., 21 envelopes (Box 7, Item 45)
    - Achilles Over the Trench. "So saying, light-foot Iris pass'd away." (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 1)
    - Adeline. "Mystery of mysteries" (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 1)
    - "As thro' the land at eve we went" (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 1)
    - Ask Me No More. "Ask me no more: the moon may draw the sea;" (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 1)
    - The Ballad of Oriana. "My heat is wasted with my woe" (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 1)
    - The Beggar Maid. "Her arms across her breast she laid;" (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 1)
    - "Birds in the high Hall-garden" (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 1)
    - Break, Break, Break. "Break, break, break" (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 1)
    - Break, Break, Break. "Break, break, break," continued (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 2)
    - Break, Break, Break. "Break, break, break," continued (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 3)
    - "But when the council broke, I rose and past" (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 3)
    - A Character. "With a half-glance upon the sky" (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 3)
    - The Charge of the Light Brigade. "Half a league, half a league" (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 3)
    - The Charge of the Light Brigade. "Half a league, half a league," continued (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 4)
    - Claribel. "Where Claribel low-lieth" (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 4)
    - "Come down, O maid, from yonder mountain height:" (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 4)
    - "Come into the garden, Maud" (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 4)
    - "Come into the garden, Maud," continued (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 5)
    - Crossing the Bar. "Sunset and evening star" (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 5)
    - The Day-Dream. "O Lady Flora, let me speak:" (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 5)
    - The Days That Are No More. "Tears, idle tears, I know not what they mean" (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 5)
    - De Profundis: "Out of the deep, my child, out of the deep" (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 5)
    - The Death of the Old Year. "Full knee-deep lies the winter snow" (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 5)
    - The Deserted House. "Life and Thought have gone away" (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 5)
    - Despair. "Is it you, that preach'd in the chapel there looking over the sand?" (Box 7, Item 45, Envelope 5)